More

* * *

Terms of Service
================

### 1\. Terms

By accessing the website at [https://bots.ondiscord.xyz](https://bots.ondiscord.xyz/), you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms of Service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.

This website is not for use by those under 13 years of age, and Bots on Discord does not knowingly store information from children under 13.

### 2\. Intellectual Property

This website and its original content, features, and functionality are owned by Brandon Russell and are protected by international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws. All data generated and shared by Bots on Discord in the past, present, or future is property of Bots on Discord and it's sole owners and must be transferred, removed, or changed on request.

### 3\. Restrictions

You are expressly and emphatically restricted from all of the following:

1. modifying or copying any website material;
2. selling, sublicensing and/or otherwise commercializing any website material;
3. attempting to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on this website;
4. removing any copyright or other proprietary notations from website materials;
5. transferring website materials to another person or "mirroring" the materials on any other server;
6. using this website in any way that is, or may be, damaging to this website;
7. using this website in any way that impacts user access to this website;
8. using this website contrary to applicable laws and regulations, or in a way that causes, or may cause, harm to the website, or to any person or business entity;
9. engaging in any data mining, data harvesting, data extracting, or any other similar activity in relation to this website, or while using this website;
10. using this website to engage in any advertising or marketing without permission from Bots on Discord or our advertising partners;

### 4\. Your Content

In these Terms of Service, "Your Content" shall mean any audio, video, text, images, or other material you choose to submit to this website. With respect to Your Content, by submitting it, you grant Bots on Discord a non-exclusive, worldwide, irrevocable, royalty-free, sublicensable license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute it in any and all media.

Your Content must be your own and must not be infringing on any third party’s rights. Bots on Discord reserves the right to remove any of Your Content from this website at any time, and for any reason, without notice.

### 5\. Termination

We may terminate your access to the website, without cause or notice, which may result in the destruction of all information associated with your account. All provisions of this agreement that, by their nature, should survive termination shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity, and limitations of liability.

### 6\. No Warranties

This website is provided "as is" with no warranty or liability for any outcomes of using the website and/or any content you may or may not interact with on the website, and you agree that Bots on Discord is not liable for any events in the past, in current times, or in the future. Bots on Discord is not responsible and will not take responsibility for the behavior of other parties using the website.

### 7\. Limitation of Liability

In no event shall Bots on Discord, nor any of its representatives, be liable to you for anything arising out of or in any way connected with your use of this website, whether such liability is under contract, tort or otherwise, and Bots on Discord, including its representatives, shall not be liable for any indirect, consequential, or special liability arising out of or in any way related to your use of this Website.

### 8\. Accuracy of Materials

The materials appearing on Bots on Discord's website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Bots on Discord does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete, or current. Bots on Discord and its users may make changes to the materials contained on the website at any time without notice. However, Bots on Discord does not make any commitment to update the materials.

### 9\. Links

This website contains links to many other websites not controlled by Bots on Discord. Bots on Discord is not responsible for the contents or behavior of such linked websites. The inclusion of links on this website does not imply endorsement by Bots on Discord. Any use of linked websites is done at the user's own risk.

### 10\. Modifications

Bots on Discord may revise these Terms of Service at any time without notice. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these terms of service.

### 11\. Governing Law

These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Arkansas and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State.

Privacy Policy
==============

At Bots on Discord one of our main priorities is the privacy and security of our visitors. This Privacy Policy contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Bots on Discord and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, please contact an admin on our Discord server at [discord.gg/bvm6vSv](https://discord.gg/bvm6vSv) or email [\[email protected\]](https://bots.ondiscord.xyz/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### Stored Data

Bots on Discord uses Discord for authentication and in place of having our own accounts. Because of this we store information about your Discord account in our secure databases. This information includes all data authorized by the user through Discord's OAuth consent page. For users with no created content this data will be deleted after a few days of inactivity. While logged in to the website, any account-linked action you perform, such as reviewing, we be stored with a reference to your Discord ID. Additionally, any data you submit to Bots on Discord, such as through bot pages, lists, or reviews, will be stored and displayed on the site until deleted by the user or a moderator.

### Anonymous Tracking

To analyze user behavior and improve our website we anonymously track some actions and send the data to [DataDog](https://www.datadoghq.com/). This data is not stored on our servers and contains no personally identifiable information.

### Third-Party Tracking

Bots on Discord uses Google Analytics to analyze use of the site. Google Analytics uses cookies and collects usage data. You may view their privacy policy [here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and opt-out with their tool [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

Bots on Discord also uses Yandex Metrica to analyze use of the site. They use cookies to track how users engage with the website. You may view their privacy policy [here](https://yandex.com/legal/confidential/) and opt-out using their extension [here](https://yandex.com/support/metrica/general/opt-out.html).

### Log Files

Bots on Discord follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, date and time stamp, and referring/exit pages. The purpose of this information is for administering the website.

### Cookies

Bots on Discord uses cookies to store information about users. These cookies store the session identifier for logged in users. This is used for authentication on the website and links you to your Discord data.

### Our Advertising Partners

* Venatus Media: [venatusmedia.com/privacy](https://www.venatusmedia.com/privacy).

Third-party ad servers or ad networks use technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Bots on Discord, which are sent directly to user's browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Bots on Discord has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy.

**Tip:** Sorting your searches by relevance give you more relevant results compared to other sorting options.

onDiscord.xyz is not affiliated with Discord Inc.

Created and owned by [Brussell](https://brussell.me/)

Tags

Links
